-(insects chittering)
-(birds chirping)
We'll be starting the
Event in one minute!
But, before we begin,
let's hear a few words
of well-appreciated
encouragement
from the always-eloquent
Utahime Iori!
What? Huh?
Well, I, uh, guess, uh,
although during this Event
some degree of injury
will be unavoidable,
you should, uh, uh,
uh, help each other out,
or something,
(chuckling) if you can?
[Gojou] Okay, sorry, time's up!
[Utahime] Ugh, Gojou
you jerk, I wasn't done!
[Gojou] Now, let the sister
school Exchange Event begin!
-(feedback squeaking)
-(energetic music)
[Utahime] You should
respect your seniors!
Ichiro?
So stupid.
Where did Toudou go?
How the hell should I know?
I'm not his babysitter!
[Kasumi] Can't we
all just get along?
(energetic rock music)
-(insects chittering)
-(birds chirping)
Where do you think
the cursed spirit boss is?
It was probably
unleashed at the midpoint
between the two groups,
but we can't expect
it to stand still.
At the pre-arranged
time, we'll all split
into the Megumi Squad
and the Panda Squad.
After that, it's on you.
Got it, Yuuji.
Got it!
(Demon Dog barking)
(creature chittering)
(creature babbling)
Just small fry.
(air whooshing)
(Demon Dog snarling)
Zen'in, stop running!
(creature chittering)
-(blow booming)
-(Toudou yelling)
Yeah, you're all together!
Now come at me, all at once!
-(Yuuji grunting)
-(footsteps thudding)
-(Toudou grunting)
-(Yuuji grunting)
-(blow crashing)
[Maki] Scatter!
(footsteps thudding)
I wonder why Toudou was alone.
I'm not too sure,
but we were right
to give Yuuji that job.
He is a monster,
that much is for sure.
Yup!
But don't worry about him now.
[Toge] Tuna.
(both grunting)
-(blow booming)
-(both grunting)
-(both thudding)
(Toudou chuckling)
(opening theme music)
(singer singing in Japanese)
Toudou will definitely be
out to crush us right away,
and Mai might just follow
him in order to get to me.
(air whooshing)
Toudou is a monster.
(body crashing)
The worst possible outcome
would be that we all face him
and we all get wiped out.
(air whooshing)
So our plan was to leave
one of us, not sure who,
either Panda or Megumi,
behind to deal with him.
So now, Itadori, we'll
leave that role to you.
[Yuuji] Hm?
We can't afford to lose
any of our better scouts.
You don't have to beat him,
just try to hold out
and buy us some time.
I say be daring against him!
To be blunt, we weren't
counting on your abilities anyway,
so it won't matter too
much if you have to quit.
Oh, thanks a lot!
I'm sorry, Megumi, I know
you wanted to take on Toudou.
No, I'm fine either way.
[Panda] You're super low-key.
I'll play along, if
you want me to.
-Hm?
-Huh?
And I'll win too.
(pensive rock music)
(Toudou growling)
(Toudou spitting)
At least your speed's decent.
[Yuuji] Seriously?
I thought I landed a good one!
(energetic rock music)
(Toudou grunting)
(knuckles cracking)
So I'll return the favor!
Act like your life's at stake!
(Yuuji grunting)
(creature chittering)
(Toudou grunting)
-(blow crashing)
-(Toudou yelling)
(Yuuji grunting)
(tree booming)
-(Yuuji crashing)
-(Yuuji groaning)
[Yuuji] My arm's still attached?
(Yuuji gagging)
I thought it got blown off!
If that cursed spirit
hadn't gotten in the way,
that would have been really bad!
(Yuuji groaning)
-(Yuuji gasping)
-(foot stomping)
-(foot stomping repeatedly)
-(Yuuji groaning)
(Toudou chuckling)
-(foot stomping repeatedly)
-(Yuuji groaning)
-(Toudou grunting)
-(foot stomping)
(Toudou chuckling)
♪ Oh oh oh oh oh oh ♪
-(insects chittering)
-(birds chirping)
All done huh?
-(Toudou grunting)
-(neck cracking)
(Toudou chuckling)
I wonder which one I
should go after now?
-(fingers scratching)
-(Toudou gasping)
-(Toudou laughing)
-(energetic electronic music)
Man, are you for real?
(Yuuji groaning)
What gives you the right
to just stomp all over
my head like that?
What if you made me even
dumber than I already was?
Don't worry about that.
Takada says, "Men are perfect
when they're a little dumb,"
and I have a
feeling she's right.
Takada?
I don't care about any idols!
Really?
So you don't care
about idols, huh?
Well, I bet you know who she is.
What's your name, first-year?
Yuuji Itadori.
All right, Yuuji Itadori.
I have one question
that I need to ask you.
(Toudou chuckling)
What kind of woman is your type?
Huh?
Uh, you wanna know my type?
Why would you be
asking me that now?
Nevermind why, I'm
just evaluating you.
Uh...
Well, I don't get
why it's important,
but I guess if I had to say,
I like a tall woman with
a nice big ass, just sayin'.
Like Jennifer Lawrence!
(Toudou gasping)
-(Toudou gasping)
-(gentle dramatic music)
-Hey, Usiji!
-Yeah, I know!
-I totally understand.
-Got my lunch money?
-Yeah, it's my lunch money!
-He doesn't even like me.
He won't talk to me.
-(pages rustling)
-(gentle guitar music)
You know what, this
new series is pretty good!
Yeah?
-(students chattering)
-My mom knows-
Huh.
[Student] I just wish
it would snow already.
-(bell chiming)
-(students chattering)
(footsteps thudding)
I'm gonna tell
Takada I love her.
Huh? No, don't do that!
Then you'd be crying
on my shoulder for days
and that would suck!
Why are you assuming
I'll get rejected?
(footsteps thudding)
An even better question is
why do you think
she'll say yes to you?
I remember something
that Anne Sullivan said
at one point to Helen Keller.
She asked her, "What
fool thinks of defeat
"before even trying?"
So-
Uh, that was Inoki?
(paper tearing)
I'm really sorry, but I'm
already in love with someone.
(footsteps thudding)
(Toudou sobbing)
[Toudou] Any chance that
the 'someone' she loves is me?
No, no chance at all, man.
Come on, let's get some ramen.
My treat, what do you say, bud?
(footsteps thudding)
(hand tapping)
(Toudou sobbing)
So you never lost to anyone
in your hometown, huh?
You and I were destined to
be best friends like we are!
Hold on, you just
learned my name!
(air whooshing)
Yeah, keep heading
the way you are.
He's with Toudou though.
Not a problem.
He was the one who told
us to do what we want.
-(air whooshing)
-(gunshot booming)
-(gunshots booming)
-(suspenseful music)
[Kasumi] New Shadow
Style, Simple Domain!
-(air whooshing)
-(footsteps thudding)
Quick Draw!
-(sword whooshing)
-(Yuuji grunting)
What reflexes!
I mean, I know I hesitated,
but my counter didn't
even scratch him!
-(air whooshing)
-(Yuuji gasping)
(energy whooshing)
[Yuuji] I'm surrounded!
Wait!
Why does it feel like these guys
(air whooshing)
are actually trying to kill me?
(hands clapping)
(both gasping)
What the hell?
-Huh?
-Did Itadori and I
just switch places?
Hey.
-(Toudou grunting)
-(blow thudding)
Didn't I tell you I'd kill you
if you interfered with me?
(scoffing) No, you didn't.
You just said you'd kill us
if we ordered you around.
Was that switch
Itadori's technique?
Or was it Toudou's?
[Toudou] Same thing!
Now piss off!
(tense music)
(footsteps thudding)
He's retreating.
How lame.
[Kasumi] Thank goodness!
Make sure you kill him.
I'd say all that
depends on Itadori.
And quit givin' orders!
[Yuuji] What's
with these people?
Trying to kill me
and then arguing with
each other about it?
It's lucky for you I'm
not an inconsiderate type
who'd ever hold back against
his best friend in a fight!
(air whooshing)
(Momo groaning)
This is why I said they
ought to leave him be.
We're off to a bad start.
We can't start hunting
down cursed spirits
without me scouting
from the air either.
(Momo sighing)
They're all just so annoying!
But hang in there, me,
you're the cutest one!
Go get her!
(electricity crackling)
Oh.
Mai, Mechamaru,
go help Nishimiya!
[Mechamaru] Right.
Yeah, we're in big trouble
without our air cover!
-(footsteps thundering)
-(suspenseful music)
(Kasumi gasping)
-(weapons clanging)
-(both grunting)
(Megumi and Noritoshi grunting)
(both grunting)
Kamo is your team
trying to kill Yuuji Itadori?
(energetic music)
(frantic music)
-(wind whooshing)
-(birds chirping)
It's odd.
This is strange.
All the Kyoto students
are moving together.
They're heading for
where we left Yuuji.
It would seem unlikely
that that's a coincidence.
Aren't they just headed
toward the cursed spirit?
No way.
Unless the special-grade
is especially cunning,
Demon Dog would've sensed it.
(Demon Dog barking)
You think...
Could they be
trying to kill Itadori?
What the hell?
How can that be?
(tense music)
It could be.
[Toge] Kelp.
I didn't sense that
level of hostility
from them when they arrived,
but that was before we
found out Yuuji was still alive.
(Nobara gasping)
(flute trilling)
It is conceivable that
Principal Gakuganji
would order this move.
So are the Kyoto
students all such cowards
they kill on someone's orders?
That's pathetic.
You have to realize
that they don't
see Yuuji the way you do.
The two of you have spent
day after day with him.
We've just become
familiar with him.
He's a good person.
I'd say he's happier than
most sorcerers I've known.
But still,
for those who don't
know anything about Yuuji,
just the fact that he's
the vessel of Sukuna
makes him an object of fear.
So for them, killing him
wouldn't feel any different
than exorcizing a curse.
Even for normal
jujutsu sorcerers,
that line can
easily get blurred.
[Maki] Megumi, we're
going back for him.
I'm sorry.
What are you
apologizing for, dummy?
If you let a friend die,
winning or losing an
event doesn't matter.
Yuuji's not answering
his phone anymore either.
Nobara and I will go back
to confirm that he's safe.
As for you, Toge, you keep
hunting the cursed spirit.
[Toge] Bonito flakes.
I know you're worried
about Yuuji too,
but if my prediction
here is correct,
the Kyoto students plan
here is to use the chaos
and confusion of this
battle to assassinate Yuuji.
Their attempts will end
as soon as the battle does.
Makes sense.
[Toge] Salmon.
I'm worried about Maki too.
We won't let them kill Yuuji,
and we're gonna win this fight!
Copy that!
(phone line beeping)
Hm?
(Nobara growling)
Why don't you answer
your phone, Fushiguro?
So lame!
Why didn't they
give us wireless radios
or at least Bluetooth earbuds?
I don't like those
things, they're distracting!
I get startled when
when calls come in.
So then you just take
'em off during combat!
(air whooshing)
(Momo crashing)
(Momo groaning)
That hurt!
So that's Fushiguro's Nue, huh?
Electrified wings.
That's gonna limit my
movement for a while.
-(blow booming)
-(Momo grunting)
♪ Nishimiya, there in a tree ♪
♪ Come down and play ♪
[Momo] Ugh, how childish!
That is not cute at all!
[Megumi] Kamo, are you
guys planning to kill Itadori?
And if I said we were?
What does it matter?
It would mean
that you've all failed.
Itadori could never be
defeated in such a short time.
We've no reason to kill him.
Yes, you do.
The major three clans
and the higher-ups.
-(blows booming)
-(birds chittering)
-(both grunting)
-(blow thudding)
-(blows thudding)
-(both grunting)
-(blow thudding)
-(Yuuji grunting)
-(punch thudding)
-(kick thudding)
-(Yuuji yelling)
-(blows thudding)
-(both grunting)
-(Yuuji grunting)
-(energetic music)
(Yuuji yelling)
(Toudou grunting)
Wow, what amazing toughness!
He's actively
using the landscape
to his advantage as well!
(Toudou gasping)
Where'd he go?
(air whooshing)
-(blow thudding)
-(Toudou grunting)
He's also quick to
set up his next move!
♪ Ah ah ah ♪
-(blows thudding)
-(both grunting)
And to top it off,
-(punch booming)
-(Toudou grunting)
he has such tremendous power!
His raw strength is
greater than mine,
despite his smaller body!
Which is why his
blows are still effective
with so little cursed energy!
And because there's
so little of that,
it's hard to read his movements!
But the way his cursed
energy hits after a time lag?
Well, that is just
that's just, it's just
Wrong!
(leaves rustling)
Was that Toudou yelling?
Yeah, it was.
Since he was up against
Yuuji, I'm starting to understand
why you failed
to finish him off.
So why'd you separate
from Noritoshi?
Is your technique a
secret from your allies too?
(sword rattling)
I am sorry about Itadori.
Not to make excuses, but
I'm really not like the others.
Still, that doesn't
mean I'm about to quit
and just let you guys
win this Exchange Event!
(upbeat music)
You know that
sorcerers advance in rank
through a recommendation
system, right?
The Exchange Event
has always been
a big deal to the sorcerers
who don't have connections
higher up the chain.
Students who perform well
here are granted many chances
to advance while
they're studying.
By rule though,
the person in charge
of a student can't
recommend them.
For instance, Gojou can't give
Yuuji Itadori a first-grade
recommendation.
I want independence
as soon as possible,
that way I can earn some money.
[Maki] Why?
-(sword rattling)
-(tense music)
Because I'm poor!
And I'm the eldest.
Yeah, but how about you?
How do you tolerate Mai?
You seem too nice.
[Kasumi] What?
Hm, yeah, I might be.
I won't hold back, you know?
That's not a problem!
I didn't tell you all that
to get your sympathy!
Listen, my friend, that
time-lagged cursed energy blast?
That is a bad habit
you've developed.
[Yuuji] Oh, you
mean Divergent Fist?
What the hell?
Where's he going with this?
If you rely on
just that one trick,
you'll never defeat me!
And if you're satisfied
staying on that level,
then sadly you and I can't
possibly stay best friends.
You okay with that?
I don't know, I
don't care about that.
[Toudou] You're okay
with staying weak?
(Yuuji gasping)
(energy whooshing)
Definitely not!
-♪ Oh oh oh oh oh oh ♪
-(tense music)
That's more like it!
My new best friend!
(closing theme music)
(singer singing in Japanese)
-Juju Stroll!
-(playful music)
(pensive music)
At minimum?
Someone who's
stronger than I am.
Huh?
What makes you think
I'd answer that question?
I totally can't stand a UBSSD.
(playful digital music)
You guys know who
Sebastian Stan is?
(Momo giggling)
His body is awesome!
Well, of course I
naturally have a thing
for hot-looking guys, just
the same as any girl would.
But, in my mind, a guy has
to be fun to hang out with!
And then, the most
important thing?
Well, he should make you feel
like he's the only one for you!
(Kasumi gasping)
(chuckling) Gosh, now I've
gone and embarrassed myself!
Uh, wait, I know!
I, ugh, I can't remember.
Uh, hold on!
You know, the girl who was nice?
Uh, the nice girl!
The girl who has the cool bangs?
Yeah, you know her!
Nice.
(steady ticking)
(beeping)
(bright chiming)
(bell dinging)
Oh! Miwa?
Oh, yeah, that's her!
(heavy metal music)